For such a tough guy, he
sure was easy to finish off.
But I guess if you think about it,
the end is usually a pretty
sudden curtain call, you know.
Most folks don't get to say goodbye,
especially when a bullet
to the brain's involved.
Ha!
Think of that as a little parting
wisdom before I make you croak.
Polnareff!
Don't let him get to you!
You're much stronger than that!
You still don't get it, do you? Mr.
Avdol told you!
He begged you not to fight alone!
But you completely ignored him.
Even if it meant dying with your enemy,
you were hell-bent on getting revenge.
He followed you because that worried him.
And this is what happened as a result!
Then tell me, what am I supposed to do?
We need to fall back for now.
Avdol was stabbed in the back
and didn't have a chance.
My sister couldn't defend
herself and was killed.
You expect me to run away and
just forget all this happened?
How can we fight them when we don't
even know what their stands can do?
Don't fight a battle that'll
only end in your death!
That's what Mr.
Avdol was trying to tell you!
Hey, come on.
Do it, little pole pole.
Why, you... Polnareff!
Calm down and slowly retreat toward me.
Got it?
That truck's our way out of here. Calm?
Calm down, you say? How?
All right.
Hey!
Polnareff!
It's your fault Avdol died, you know.
I think that means you owe him.
It only seems fair.
Your friend bit the dust because of you.
Damn you, you bastard.
Where's your real body?
Polnareff, calm down.
But there's no need to be sad.
Actually, you should be happy.
You're about to see
your dear friend again.
You'll soon be dead, and then you can
enjoy the afterlife with those two fools.
You're welcome.
I have to say, your
sister was so very sweet.
Once you're reunited with your sister, Be
sure to ask her exactly how I killed her.
We had such a ball.
Klonorath, don't fall for his tricks.
He wants you to attack.
Master!
Oh, didn't you know?
Your chariot cannot cut my hanged man.
I'm in the mirror where your
stand can't go that's why.
So close and yet so far away.
Whole horse fire away let's put
an end to this idiot aye aye sir!
Die!
Hammer roll! Flash!
What the?
Wait, he's shot! Hold around!
Cuckooing, was it?
Not bad, partner.
That's out of my stance range.
Even if I got him from here, the bullet
wouldn't hit him with very much force.
He went after them, huh?
Well, I'll be.
He must really have it in for Polnareff.
I'm so sorry, Kakuhin.
It's just that...
I thought so long as I could avenge my
sister, I wouldn't care if I lived or died.
But I understand now.
I know Avdol was fighting for me.
His sacrifice won't be for naught.
I'll fight to keep on living.
You sure that you really
mean that, Polnareff?
Oui.
That's all I'm giving you is proof
that we've made up, Polnareff.
Right.
Merci, Kakyoin.
When those bastards come after us again,
I swear we'll defeat them together.
Avdol, my old friend.
You know,
I was so sure that I stabbed him with
my sword, but my strike never hit him.
It was like he wasn't there.
Even breaking the mirror
into pieces didn't stop him.
The hanged man just
attacked from the shards.
How in the hell am I supposed
to fight against that?
He attacks your reflection.
But his knife sinks into your real flesh
and my stand can't go inside mirrors
How are we supposed to attack him if he's
in some kind of mirror world damn it?
Polnareff you keep talking about
inside the mirror in the mirror
world But there's no such thing
as a world in a mirror remember.
This is reality not fantasy
What are you talking about you saw it too?
Didn't you you can only see him in a mirror
and when you turn around he's gone Yes.
But anything that you see in a mirror
is just a reflection created by light.
I'm not an idiot!
You don't have to tell me that!
Listen, I mean this case.
I'm talking about what's going on now.
If Stans can exist in this world,
there could be a mirror world too.
There isn't.
Come on, man!
I think that fact is what's going to help
us solve the mystery of Hanged Man. Look,
Stans are able to destroy other Stans,
so there still has to be something
we don't know about his...
Hmm?
Polnareff!
The chrome of the steering wheel!
What?
The bastards caught up to us!
Look out!
Hey, are you okay?
Talk to me. I...
I slammed my chest, but I'll be fine.
What?
Charion!
Kick, avoid the reflection!
Damn. I got it.
I just saw him do it.
He's going from mirror to mirror.
This guy moves by jumping around,
one reflection to another.
He traveled all this way by
reflecting over and over.
It's the only explanation
for how he caught up to us.
Reflecting?
That means he's actually light.
Are you saying that the true
nature of his stand is light?
I am.
I just saw him in the car's bumper.
He's going to reflect off that
surface and onto something else.
Stay clear of reflective stuff.
Take anything shiny off your
body and your uniform button.
Hey, mister, are you guys okay?
Want me to bring you some medicine?
We're fine.
Look, it's dangerous.
Get out of here.
Whoa, you guys totally messed up your car.
Hey, you're bleeding, mister.
Are you sure you're okay?
That asshole!
He's reflected in the kid's eye!
Listen, kid, don't look at us! Huh?
I told you, don't look at us!
Don't follow me with your eyes!
Huh?
But your heart!
I'm fine, see?
Perfectly fine, got it?
So go look over there! But...
but you're bleeding!
You brat, I said look over there!
Huh?
Damn you, Xeniphaled!
What are you going to do?
You wouldn't poke out this cute little
kid's eye with that sword of yours,
would you?
Polnareff!
And now I finally got you!
You can't run anymore.
Not unless you gouge the kid's eyes out.
You disgusting, cruel son
of a bitch! You're dead!
Don't worry, Kakyoini.
Mon frere, that's not what
you say at a time like this.
Listen, in times like these, you've
got to say something fitting.
Before you get your revenge,
say something like this here.
My name is Jean-Pierre Polnareff.
For the honor of my dearest sister's soul,
and so my good friend Avdol can
rest peacefully in heaven above?
I'm going to hurl you into
the depths of despair!
Prepare yourself, centerfold!
Sorry about this, kid.
I'll buy you whatever
candy you want, okay?
You got dead in my eyes!
What the?
Polnareff, he's in your eye!
I don't really understand how, but he
essentially moves at the speed of light.
No one can normally see speed like that.
But then, I knew that if the kid closed
his eyes, the next move would be to my eye.
There was no other place for him to
go, and that's how we'll beat him.
Oh, I see.
Hanged man can only exist
within the world of reflection.
When one world is about to be destroyed,
he must migrate to
another reflective object.
So, as long as I can read his trajectory,
I can slice through him like butter!
His real body is over there.
You bastard. Finally.
Finally!
At last we meet.
Centerfold!
My name is Jean-Pierre Polnareff,
and I've seen through your
stand's clever little trick.
It's a stand of light that
moves at extraordinary speed.
I know there's no way that I can catch it,
but if I can predict where your
stand's going to jump next,
and I slash its trajectory in
that moment, I can cut you.
If Kakyoin and Avdol hadn't shown up,
I probably wouldn't have figured that
out and you would have killed me.
No, Polnareff!
This isn't the man with
a pair of right hands!
That's not Cinderbolt!
What the hell?
Polnareff!
Over here!
I'm centerfold, insignificant fool!
At last!
That man is some beggar who was in
the wrong place at the wrong time.
I just carved a small wound in him, the
same wound you were so gracious to give me.
You totally fell for it.
Getting close to him without knowing
what I look like was a grave mistake.
One you'll pay for with your limes!
You bastard!
Take this! Emerald!
Whoa!
Wait now!
Take a good look around you!
Hey!
Gather round!
See these two gentlemen?
They say they've got a
boatload of cash to share!
what you'll give us money for nothing huh?
such generosity you have?
such big heart? thank you!
have you figured out what's going on yet?
you say you figured out my stand?
you fool?
you think i don't know my own weakness?
i have no weakness?
you can never know
where i'll jump to next?
don't look?
don't stare at us!
please?
just look away!
you can't run anymore!
what are you going to do?
blow everyone up!
you sacrificed your entire youth?
just taught me down?
and just when you're close?
you're going?
to fail to avenge your sister?
How pathetic and sad. Meanwhile,
I, Centrifold, will continue a life surrounded
by young beauties, like your sister.
I can see it now.
Oh, the pleasures.
Come to think of it, that
sweet sister of yours
was really good at sobbing.
Farewell.
Why, you?
Polnarex.
You could do better than that. Huh?
Why you isn't what you say?
When taking revenge, you
have to be more refined.
This is what you say.
My name is Noriaki Kakyoin.
In order to avenge my dear friend Avdol,
so that the soul of my friend Polnarev's
sister may rest in peace for all eternity?
I will have you pay with your life.
I'll give this gold coin to
whoever picks it up. Behold!
A coin so perfect, it
shines like a mirror!
Yeah, now I see.
Looks like all of their eyes are
focused on one point now. Yeah.
We know the trajectory that
Hanged Man will have to take.
Merci, Capuin!
Now!
Hold it!
It won't open!
Looks like you're the one who's
really good at sobbing, Centerfold.
and you're about to plummet into hell,
begging and crying the whole way down.
But there's one thing I can't rely
on the Guardians of Hell to do.
And that's to turn your
body into a pincushion.
I've been waiting years for this moment.
I'll leave the rest to
the devil, rot in hell.
So this is the true hanged man, huh?
He was rotten all the way to the core.
I got my revenge.
Hold it!
Finally caught up with you!
Why are you walking so slow?
If you're gonna run, run
like your lives depend on it.
It's way more fun.
Isn't that right, Mr. Cinefold?
Better say your prayers, boys.
This is where your lives come to an end.
Come at us with everything
you've got, understand?
It's so boring if you just stand
there and die. Right, Mr. Centerfold?
Hey, Mr.
Centerfold, aren't you going to play?
I don't think he's listening
anymore, cowboy. Huh?
He's quite busy at the moment.
Carrying out his sentence in hell.
Don't try to pull that nonsense.
Bluffing won't work on me.
Nice try, though.
There's no way you could have beaten him.
Even I wouldn't try my
luck against that mother.
You know, Polnareff, your
sense of humor stinks.
That piece of shit's corpse is 2 or 3,000
meters that way if you
want to take a look.
Huh?
Okay, I will. Huh?
You're running away?
I don't stand a chance.
I'm at a total disadvantage by myself.
I'm hightailing it out of here,
waiting for a better chance.
Or better yet, waiting till I find
myself another partner in crime.
It's all about being number two.
That's the motto I like to live by.
Got a problem with it.
What?
Mr.
Joestar, Jotaral!
We already know about
Avdol. What a tragedy.
We didn't have a lot of time to do much
for him, but we gave him a proper funeral.
The one who stabbed Mr.
Avdol in the back was the
man with two right hands.
But the cause of death
was Whole Horse's bullet.
What should we do with him?
I'll give him his sentence!
DEATH!
Please run, Sir Hall Horse!
I'll hold him up for you!
The hell?
Get off, lady!
I don't know what exactly is going on here,
but I do know I will always protect you!
You are my everything,
darling! Please run! Hurry!
Let go of me, stupid bitch!
Come on!
What are you doing? Jotaro! Kakyoin!
Don't let Hull Horse get away!
It's too late.
Very well said, my little sweetheart.
I'll gladly accept your
feelings and keep on living.
Remember, I'm only running
away because I love you, baby!
Forever and ever!
Why, you!
Come back here!
Oh, don't you dare aww at me!
Polnareff!
That woman is just another
one of his victims.
And he no longer had any
intention of fighting with us.
We have no time to deal with him.
Evdal is gone now.
But we have to forge ahead.
It's already been fifteen days.
We don't have time to waste.
Damn it.
Guess it can't be helped.
Alright, we continue onward to Egypt.
Listen up.
In order to defeat Dio,
we have to fight as one.
We can't go off on our own, or we'll play
right into the enemy's hands. Got it?
Let's get a move on!
Good grief.
All the old paintings on the tomb.
They do the sand dance, don't you know?
If they move too quick.
They're falling down like a domino.
All the birds are men by the Nile.
They've got their money on a bed.
Called crocodiles.
They snap their teeth on your cigarette.
Falling tight to the hookah. I say.
Walk like an Egyptian.
The blonde waitresses.
Take their trays.
Spin around and they cross the floor.
They've got the moves.
You drop, you drink.
Then they bring you more.
All the school kids so sick of books.
They're like the punk and the metal band.
When the buzzer rings.
They're walking like an Egyptian.
All the kids in the marketplace say. Walk
like
an Egyptian.
We're almost there.
The city of Varanasi. Varanasi!
I got him!
I'm Joseph Joestar, an American! What?
I love you.
Hey, doesn't that sort of
look like a person's face?
Show me me!